RG 005:029, Office of the Governor: Raymond E. Baldwin (1943-1946)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Subject Files, 1946-10
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 451)
  - Charter Oak Bridge (Box 451)
  - Child Care Center (Box 451)
  - Child Study Clinic (Box 451)
  - Chiropody Board (Box 451)
  - Chiropractic (Box 451)
  - Circus Catastrophe - Hartford July 6, 1944 (Box 451)
  - City Courts (Box 451)
  - Civil Air Patrol (Box 451)
  - Civilian Production Administration (Box 451)
  - Claims against the State of Conn. (Box 451)
  - Clyma, Carl [Connecticut Servicemen's Commemorative Booklet] (Box 451)
  - Coast Guard (Box 451)
  - Colchester Election to be held to Elect Someone to Succeed Judge Shugre who is resigning (Box 451)
  - Commentary on Newsreel "We Need Job-Makers" by Governor Baldwin and "We, the People" Program, 1945 October 21 (Box 451)
  - Commerce Department (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study the Aged and Chronically Ill (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study the Probate Court System (Box 451)
  - Commissioners of Steamship Terminals (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study Highway System (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study Human Resources in Connecticut (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study the Judicial System (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study the Need for a New Haven and West Haven Port Authority (Box 451)
  - Commission to Study the Organization for Peace (Box 451)
  - Commission, Trustees of Inebriate (Box 451)
  - Commissions Created by the 1943 General Assembly (Box 451)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 451)
  - Community Service Center, Bridgeport (Box 451)
  - Comptroller's Department (Box 452)
  - Compulsory Peacetime Military Training (Box 452)
  - Conference on Food, Hotel Roosevelt, New York, 1945 June 22 (Box 452)
  - Conference on State Defense (Box 452)
  - Congressional Representatives - Corresp. (Box 452)
  - Congressmen - Correspondence (Box 452)
  - Congressmen, Meeting with, at Hartford Club Re: Milk, Feed, Food & Fuel Situations, 1943 September 2 (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Council of Churches (Box 452)
  - Connecticut, Facts About (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Food Producing Committee (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Forum - Ralph Dellaselva Record Cut, "Reconversion" [transcript] - For Use August 27, 1945 (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Labor Management Commission (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Laundry Owners' Association (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Hospital Service (Box 452)
  - Connecticut League of Women Voters (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Marketing Authority (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Mercantile Wage Board (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Plan for Hospital Care (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Prison Association (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Products (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (Box 452)
  - Connecticut Reformatory [Includes Minutes of Meetings and Superintendent's recommendations.] (Box 453)
  - Connecticut Safety Society (Box 453)
  - Connecticut Society for Crippled Children and Adults (The Workshop) (Box 453)
  - Connecticut State Employees' Association (Box 453)
  - Connecticut State Teachers' Association (Box 453)
  - Conservation (Box 453)
  - Consul Generals (Box 453)
  - Corn Situation (Box 453)
  - Council of State Government [Comprises half of the box.] (Box 453)
  - Council of State Governments Insurance Committee (Box 454)
  - Council of State Governments - State-Local Relations (Box 454)
  - County Agents (Box 454)
  - County Commissioners (Box 454)
  - County Homes (Box 454)
  - County Jails (Box 454)
  - County Sheriffs (Box 454)
  - Dairy and Food Commission (Box 454)
  - Danbury Election (Box 454)
  - Danbury Traffic Court (Box 454)
  - Danielson Town Court (Box 454)
  - Defense Council (Box 454)
  - Defense Council - Agriculture (Box 454)
  - Defense Council - Forest Fire Service (Box 454)
  - Defense Council - Hospital Div. (Box 454)
  - Defense Council - Salvage Committee (Box 454)
  - Defense Council - Transportation (Box 454)
  - Deficiency Appropriations Bill (Box 454)
  - Dental Commission (Box 454)
  - Development Commission, 4 folders (Box 454)
  - Development Commission American Symphony Movie (Box 455)
  - Development Commission Bulletins (Box 455)
  - Development Commission Letters to Mr. Edwards - People (Box 455)
  - Development Commission Zoning Matters (Box 455)
  - Directories (Box 455)
  - Domestic Animals (Box 455)
  - Education (Box 455)
  - Education Approved School (Box 455)
  - Education Dept. [2 folders] [Comprises half of the box.] (Box 455)
  - Education - Norwalk School Situation (Box 455)
  - Education - Post-War Planning (Box 455)
  - Education - Public School Building Commission (Box 455)
  - Education - School Equalization Matters (Box 455)
  - Education - Stamford School Situation (Box 455)
  - Electric Boat Company Strike (Box 456)
  - Employees' Retirement Commission (Box 456)
  - Enfield Dam (Box 456)
  - Extradition Cases (Box 456)
  - Extradition - Robert W. Chambers (Box 456)
  - Farm Labor (Box 456)
  - Federal Legislation (Box 456)
  - Federal Legislation - Aeronautics, 2 folders (Box 456)
  - Federal Legislation - Food Taxes (Box 456)
  - Federal Legislation - Insurance (Box 456)
  - Federal Works Agency (Box 456)
  - Feed Situation (Box 456)
  - Finance Advisory Committee, 2 folders (Box 456)
  - Finance and Control (Box 456)
  - Finance and Control, 1943 (Box 456)
  - Finance and Control, 1944 (Box 456)
  - Finance and Control, 1945 (Box 456)
  - Finance and Control, 1946 (Box 456)
  - Fire Prevention and Control Meeting, Old Senate Chamber, State Capitol, 1946 January 14 (Box 457)
  - Fiscal Problems (Box 457)
  - Fish and Game Dept., 1943-1944 (Box 457)
  - Fish and Game Dept., 1945 (Box 457)
  - Fish and Game Dept., 1946 (Box 457)
  - Fishers Island (Box 457)
  - Fitch's Home, Noroton (Box 457)
  - Flood Commission of Hartford (Box 457)
  - Flood Control (Box 457)
  - Flood Control Project, Hartford (Box 457)
  - Food Distribution Administration (Box 457)
  - Food - State Institutions (Box 457)
  - Foot Guard (Box 457)
  - Foreign Policy Association (Box 457)
  - Forest and Wildlife Commission (Box 457)
  - Forestry Dept. (Box 457)
  - Forfeited Rights (Box 457)
  - Forsberg Manufacturing Company (Box 457)
  - Fort Griswold - Groton Monument Association (Box 457)
  - Freight Rates (Box 457)
  - Fuel, 2 folders (Box 457)
  - Fuel - Motor (Box 458)
  - Gasoline for State Boards and Communications (Box 458)
  - Gasoline Tax (Box 458)
  - Gasoline Motors (Box 458)
  - Geological & Natural History Survey (Box 458)
  - GI Bill of Rights (Box 458)
  - Government in CT, Outline of (Box 458)
  - [Governors" Conference] Governors (PUT FOOTNOTE in FA IN A NOTE) (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Conference of Executive Committee of the Governors' Conference, Hotel Statler, Washington, 1945 January 4, 7 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Hartford, Conn. - Flood Control, October 22-23 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Meeting of the Executive Committee (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Fuel-Boston, Mass., 1945 February 2 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Matters to be taken up Chicago, 1945 November 16-17 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Proposed Pacific Trip (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Hershey, Pennsylvania - Proposed Resolutions, 1944 May (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Chicago, Shoreland Hotel - Chicago, 1944 December (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Boston - Reconversion, 1945 August 20-21 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Hershey, Pennsylvania - Resolutions Passed by the Governors Re: War Effort, etc, 1944 May (Box 458)
  - [Governors Conference] Boston - NE, 1943 December 16 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Boston, Mass., 1946 April 26 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Boston, 1946 November 21-22 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Chicago, Illinois, 1945 November 16-17 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Columbus, O., 1943 June 19-24 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Mackinac Island, Michigan, 1945 July 1-4 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] Oklahoma City, 1946 May 22-29 (Box 458)
  - [Governors' Conference] New England Governors (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] New England Governors Freight Rate Committee (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] Matters to be taken up at the New England Governors' Conference - Hotel Statler, Boston, 1945 November 15-16 (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] New England Governors, Boston, 1943 November 18-19 (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] Hotel Statler, Boston, Mass., 1945 January 3 (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] Boston, 1944 November 16-17 (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] Lighthouse Inn, New London, 1943 April 15-16 (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] Hershey, Pennsylvania, 1944 May 28-31 (Box 459)
  - [Governors' Conference] Michigan, 1945 (Box 459)
  - Governor's Mansion (Box 459)
  - Governor's Mansion Visitors (Box 459)
  - Granby Election - Judge of Probate (Box 459)
  - Groton - New London Bridge Commission (Box 459)
  - Harbor Commissioners, Board of (Box 459)
  - Hartford Bridge Commission (Box 459)
  - Hartford Hospital Fund (Box 459)
  - Health Dept., 1943 (Box 459)
  - Health Dept., 1944 (Box 459)
  - Health Dept., 1945 (Box 459)
  - Health Dept., 1945 (Box 459)
  - Health Dept. - Burton Bill S. 191 (Box 460)
  - Health Dept. Commission to Survey Hospitals and Public Health Centers (Box 460)
  - Health Dept. Control of Dusts, Gases and Fumes (Standards of Industrial Safety) (Box 460)
  - Highway Commissioner, Biennial Report of the State, 1945-1946 (Box 460)
  - Highway Dept., 1944 (Box 460)
  - Highway Dept., 1945 (Box 460)
  - Highway Dept., 1946 (Box 460)
  - Highway Dept. Cornwall Bridge (Box 460)
  - Highway Dept. Shelton Highway (Box 460)
  - Highway Dept. - Washington - Boston Hgwy (Box 460)
  - Highway - Federal Appropriation Post - War Highway Building (Box 460)
  - Highway - Planning Survey (Box 460)
  - Highway - Proposed Express Highway in Fairfield County (Box 460)
  - Highway Safety Commission (Box 461)
  - Highway Safety Conference called by President Truman to be held in Washington, 1946 May 8-10 (Box 461)
  - History of Connecticut in World War II (Box 461)
  - Hi-Y & Youth in Government Movement (Box 461)
  - Holloran, Mary (Box 461)
  - Homeopathic Medical Examining Board (Box 461)
  - Hooker, Notes from Thomas's Sermons (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Fairfield State Hospital, 1943 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Fairfield State Hospital, 1944 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Fairfield State Hospital, 1945 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Fairfield State Hospital, 1946 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Laurel Heights Sanitarium (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Long Lane Farm (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Mansfield Training School & Hospital, 1943 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Mansfield Training School & Hospital, 1944 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Mansfield Training School & Hospital, 1945 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Mansfield Training School & Hospital, 1946 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Mansfield Training School and Hospital - Correspondence Re: Difficulty with Institution Heads (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Middletown Hospital (Connecticut State Hospital), 1943 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Middletown Hospital (Connecticut State Hospital), 1944 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Middletown Hospital (Connecticut State Hospital), 1945 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Middletown Hospital (Connecticut State Hospital), 1946 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Norwich State Hospital, 1943 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Norwich State Hospital, 1944 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Norwich State Hospital, 1945 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Norwich State Hospital, 1946 (Box 461)
  - [Hospitals] Schools for the Deaf (Box 462)
  - [Hospitals] Seaside Sanitarium (Box 462)
  - [Hospitals] Southbury Training School (Box 462)
  - Hospitals for World War II Veterans (Box 462)
  - Hospitals, Mental (Box 462)
  - Housing (Box 462)
  - Housing - General Correspondence Housing Problems, 1945 (Box 462)
  - Housing - General Correspondence Housing Problems, 1946 (Box 462)
  - Housing - Correspondence with Mr. White, Mr. Dobbs and Mr. Wyatt, 1945 (Box 462)
  - Housing - Correspondence with Mr. White, Mr. Dobbs and Mr. Wyatt, 1946 (Box 462)
  - Housing Authority (Box 462)
  - Housing Authority - Advisory Committee on (Box 462)
  - Housing Authority - Noroton Heights (Box 462)
  - Housing Reports on Vacancies (Box 462)
  - Housing and Reorganization (Box 462)
  - Hurricane, 1944 September 14 (Box 462)
  - Ickes, Harold L. - P. A. W. (Box 462)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 462)
  - Income Tax (Box 462)
  - Insurance Dept., 1943-1944 (Box 462)
  - Insurance Dept., 1945 (Box 462)
  - Insurance Dept., 1946 (Box 462)
  - Inter-American Conference (Box 463)
  - Inter-American Conference, 1944 May (Box 463)
  - Inter-American Conference - Acceptances of Invitations, 1944 May 21-23 (Box 463)
  - Inter-American Dinner - Invitations, Acceptances, & Regrets, 1944 April 11 (Box 463)
  - Intergovernmental Cooperation Commission (Box 463)
  - Internal Revenue Dept. United States (Box 463)
  - Inter-Racial Commission, 8 folders (Box 463)
  - Inter-Racial Commission - Letters to be referred to this Committee (Box 463)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 463)
  - Interstate Sanitation Commission (Box 463)
  - Iron Ore Deposits (Box 463)
  - Israel Putnam Memorial Park Commission (Box 463)
  - Jackson, John Day - New Haven Register (Box 463)
  - Job Makers (Box 463)
  - Job Makers Luncheon - Hartford Club, 1945 November 28 (Box 463)
  - Job Seekers (Box 464)
  - Johnson, Curtiss [President, The Shore Line Publishing Co. Inc.] (Box 464)
  - Judicial Commission (Box 464)
  - Judiciary (Box 464)
  - Junior College of Connecticut (Box 464)
  - Juvenile Court (Box 464)
  - Kellems, Vivian [Republican advocating the retention of women in factories and Enactment of an Equal Rights Amendment to the U. S. Constitution] (Box 464)
  - Labor Department, 1943 (Box 464)
  - Labor Department, 1944 (Box 464)
  - Labor Department, 1945 (Box 464)
  - Labor Department, 1946 (Box 464)
  - Labor Dept. - Division of Unemployment Comp[ensation], 1943 (Box 464)
  - Labor Dept. - Division of Unemployment Comp[ensation], 1944 (Box 464)
  - Labor Dept. - Division of Unemployment Comp[ensation], 1945 (Box 464)
  - Labor Dept. - Division of Unemployment Comp[ensation], 1946 (Box 464)
  - Labor Department - Employment of Minors - Correspondence (Box 465)
  - Labor Dept. - Employment Service (Box 465)
  - Labor Dept. - Labor Wage Board (Box 465)
  - Labor Department - Releases (Box 465)
  - Labor Department - Strikes (Box 465)
  - Labor Department - U. C. Advisory Council (Box 465)
  - Labor Management Board (Box 465)
  - Labor Relations Board (state) (Box 465)
  - Labor - Return of Employment Services to the States) (Box 465)
  - Leases (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Aeronautics, An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Agriculture (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Aircraft, Regulation of Intra-State Transportation of Persons - Property for Hire (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Airports, Municipal (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Airport Zoning, An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Creating an Appropriation in Aid of Vocational Schools and Adult Educational Activity (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Appropriations Committee (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Aviation (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Bills - Special Session (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Board of Administrative Research & Planning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Board of Pardons, Amending An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Special Session Bonus for Servicemen (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Care of Mentally Ill Persons, An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Committee (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Connecticut Commerce Commission (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Cooperative Marketing Associations, Amending An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Danbury Traffic Court, An Act Concerning Abolishing (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Farm & Equipment Purchases Assistance, Providing for (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Fine Arts Commission, Creation of (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Fishers Island, Return of, to Connecticut (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Food Emergency, An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Fuel Emergency (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Governor's War Powers (Box 465)
  - Legislation - (Grants) (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Grants to Municipalities for Planning Public Works Projects, Appropriations to the Public Works Fund (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Grants to Municipalities, Public Works Projects, An Act Concerning (Box 465)
  - Legislation - "Great Trail" or Old Connecticut Path, An Act Providing for a Committee to Study (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Highway Fund, Investment of Cash Balance (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Inebriates, Study, Treatment and Care of (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Labor Relations (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Liquor Control Bills (Box 465)
  - Legislation - List of Bills Prepared by Mr. Brown (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Mentally Ill Persons, An Act Concerning (Private Boarding Houses) (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Merit System (Appeals) (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Milk (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Mother's and Father's Day (Box 465)
  - Legislation - (A Connecticut) Port Survey Commission (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Postwar Planning Board, Extending Existence of (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Program of Work, Job Training, Education, Unemployed Citizens, Establishment of, An Act Authorizing (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Public School Building, State Aid for (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Public Works (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Railroads, Promotion of Safety of Employees & Travelers (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Record in War (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Retirement (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Rules of the Road, Amending Act (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Social Protection Commission, Creation of (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Soldiers, Sailors and Marines Fund, Provision for Increasing (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Special Legislation To Be Considered By 1945 General Assembly (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Special Session (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Special Session 1944 House Journals (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Special Session 1944 Senate Journals (Box 465)
  - Legislation - State Geological & Natural History Survey, Amending an Act (Box 465)
  - Legislation - State Park and Forest Com[mission] Appropriation-Equipment, Wages and Reforestation (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Teachers (Box 465)
  - Legislation - U.S. Senate Vacancy, Authorization to Fill (Box 465)
  - Legislation - "Veteran," Defining (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Veteran Reemployment and Advisory Commission (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Voting, Separately for Each Candidate on Ballots and Voting Machine (Box 465)
  - Legislation - War Orders (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Water Resources, to Provide Improvement, Development, Conservation of (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Workmen's Compensation Act - Time of Beginning of Compensation, An Act Amending (Box 465)
  - Legislation - Workmen's Compensation Law - Rate of Compensation, An Act Amending (Box 465)
  - Legislative Council (Box 466)
  - Legislative Council - Committee to Study Problem of Criminally Insane and Insane Criminals (Box 466)
  - Prospective Special Legislative Session (Box 466)
  - Special Session of Legislature Re: Housing, 1946 (Box 466)
  - Special Session of Legislature Re: Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 466)
  - Special Session of Legislature Re: Salary Increases, 1946 (Box 466)
  - Letters of Introduction (Box 466)
  - Letters to Licensing Boards Re: Returning Veterans (Box 466)
  - Levy, Joseph [Associate Attorney General Post] (Box 466)
  - Library, State (Box 466)
  - Liquor Control Act (Box 466)
  - Liquor Control Commission (Box 466)
  - Lithuania (Box 466)
  - Man and Woman Power (Box 466)
  - Manpower Meeting-March 30, 1943 (Box 466)
  - Manpower-Textile Industry (Box 466)
  - Manufacturers Association (Box 466)
  - March of Youth (Box 466)
  - Marine Historical Museum (Box 466)
  - Maritime Association (Box 466)
  - Maritime Day (Box 466)
  - Maritime School, New London, Conn. (Box 466)
  - Marot Junior College (Box 466)
  - Marriage Laws (Box 466)
  - Marshall, Alice [Civil Service Position with U. S. Employment Service Office] (Box 467)
  - Masonic Service Association (Box 467)
  - Massa, S. John [President, Small Manufacturer's Association of Connecticut, Inc.] (Box 467)
  - McCarran Report Hearing (Box 467)
  - McGraw-Hill Publishing Co. (Box 467)
  - Mead - Resignation from Senate (Box 467)
  - Meat Situation, 2 folders (Box 467)
  - Mediation Board (Box 467)
  - Medical Examining Board (Box 467)
  - Medical Journal (Box 467)
  - Medical Society, Connecticut State (Box 467)
  - Memorial Day (Box 467)
  - Memorial to Veterans (Box 467)
  - Merchant Marine (Box 467)
  - Meriden Child Care project (Box 467)
  - Meriden School for Boys (Box 467)
  - Merit System (Box 467)
  - Merritt Highway Commission (Box 467)
  - Merritt Highway - Museums (Box 467)
  - Metropolitan District Commission (Box 467)
  - Middletown Probate Court (Box 467)
  - Middletown - Proposed Hotel & Restaurant (Box 467)
  - Miles, Sherman [Major - General, U. S. Army Headquarters, First Service Command, Boston, Re: Transfer of arms confiscated by civilian law enforcement agencies to the U.S. Army] (Box 467)
  - Milford Town Court (Box 467)
  - Military Affairs (Box 467)
  - Milk Administration (Box 467)
  - Milk Coordinator (Box 467)
  - Milk - Governor's Correspondence and Conferences with Washington Officials (Box 467)
  - Milk Producers' Council (Box 467)
  - Milk Regulation Board (Box 467)
  - Milk Situation (Box 467)
  - Milk Strike (Box 467)
  - Moral Rearmament (Box 468)
  - Morgenthau - Com[mission] on Intergovernmental Fiscal Relations (Box 468)
  - Motor Vehicle Department (Box 468)
  - Music Week (Box 468)
  - National Clothing Drive (Box 468)
  - National Discussion Contest (Box 468)
  - National Economic Council (Box 468)
  - National Freedom Day (Box 468)
  - National Income - Average Salary for Employees (Box 468)
  - National Labor Relations Board (Box 468)
  - National Safety Council (Box 468)
  - National Service Fund (Box 468)
  - National War Labor Board (Box 468)
  - Nautical Cadets (Box 468)
  - Naval Guard (Box 468)
  - Naval Militia (Box 468)
  - Naval Reserve (Box 468)
  - Navy Day, 1946; 2 folders (Box 468)
  - Navy - LST Division Ceremonies and Dinner, 1946 July 29 (Box 468)
  - Negro Leaders (Box 468)
  - Nevada Livestock Quarantine (Box 468)
  - New England Air Mail Week, 1946 July 1-6 (Box 468)
  - New England Council (Box 468)
  - New England Highway Safety Commission (Box 468)
  - New Haven Park Commission (Box 468)
  - New Haven Post - War Council (Box 468)
  - New Haven Probate Court Election to Fill Vacancy Caused by the Death of Judge Gilson (Box 468)
  - New Haven State Teachers' College (Box 468)
  - New Haven - West Haven Port Authority (Box 468)
  - New London County Home [Proposed Plans for the Use of the New London County Home by Norwich State Hospital and Children's Observation Home] (Box 468)
  - New London Hospital Case - Lawrence and. Memorial Hospital (Box 468)
  - New London Tercentenary (Box 468)
  - Niles-Bement-Pond (Box 468)
  - Norwalk - Absentee Voting (Box 468)
  - Norwalk Tire & Rubber Co. (Box 468)
  - Nurses, Board of Examiners (Box 468)
  - Nutrition Commission (Box 468)
  - Office of Civilian Defense (Box 469)
  - Office of Defense Transportation (Box 469)
  - Office of Price Administration (Box 469)
  - Office of War Information (Box 469)
  - Office of War Mobilization (Box 469)
  - Old Lyme - Old Saybrook Bridge Commission (Box 469)
  - Old Saybrook (Box 469)
  - Optometry Board (Box 469)
  - Park and Forest Commission (Box 469)
  - Parole Board (Box 469)
  - Paroles and Probationers (Box 469)
  - Personnel Appeal Board (Box 469)
  - Personnel, Consultants on (Box 469)
  - Personnel Dept., 1943-1944 (Box 469)
  - Personnel Dept., 1945 (Box 469)